{
    "subject": "resource/PRTM",
    "predicate": "ontology/location",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "PRTM is located in United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8883458375930786,
            "question": "Where is PRTM located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8864691853523254,
            "question": "Is PRTM in North America?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.864274799823761,
            "question": "What state is PRTM located in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7645959258079529,
            "question": "In which country is PRTM situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7073830366134644,
            "question": "What is the geographical location of PRTM?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5662333369255066,
            "question": "What is the climate like where PRTM is located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5529062151908875,
            "question": "Are there any notable landmarks near PRTM?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5044242739677429,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about PRTM's headquarters?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49716079235076904,
            "question": "Is PRTM near any major cities?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30065691471099854,
            "question": "Does PRTM operate globally?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=PRTM is located in United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6164_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is PRTM near any major cities?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6164_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about PRTM's headquarters?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6164_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any notable landmarks near PRTM?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6164_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6164_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6164_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6164_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6164_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6164_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6164_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6164_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6164_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6164_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6164_82.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents state that PRTM Management, which is the subject of the queries related to location, is located in Waltham, United States. Therefore, the triple \"PRTM is located in United States\" is supported by the given information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}